Finding Aid for the American Civil Liberties Union of Southern California Records LSC.0900
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Subject Files
  - People v. Thornton, Capital Punishment f. 1, Hill, Robert Douglas, n.d. (Box 783)
  - Capital punishment f. 2-4, People v. Baker, Hill v. Nelson, n.d. (Box 784)
  - Letha, Tonya, n.d. (Box 785)
  - Liverman, Ron, n.d. (Box 785)
  - Alex Cota v. County of L.A. (amicus curiae), n.d. (Box 785)
  - Cortines v. Scott Part I, n.d. (Box 785)
  - Elam v. Los Angeles Board of Education, n.d. (Box 785)
  - Moriarty, Patrick -- Pesqueria, Doreen, n.d. (Box 786)
  - Fonda v. Nixon, Carl v. City of Los Angeles (Box 786)
  - Physicians, Standards, Legal Issues (Box 787)
  - Dillard v. Pitchess f. 1,2, n.d. (Box 787)
  - Dillard v. Pitchess f. 3, Brown v. Pitchess, People v. Anderson. Carl v. City of Los Angeles (Box 788)
  - Juvenile, Non-profits, Public Assistance, Rescissions, Trust Deeds, Housing, n.d. (Box 789)
  - Aubry, Ernest L. - materials on student law, n.d. (Box 789)
  - Sitkin, Peter E. and Vanaman, Valerie - materials on welfare agency practice and procedure (Box 789)
  - Prepaid medical plans, Consumer, Bond Waiver Employment, Health (Box 790)
  - Smerling, Terry - contracts notebook, n.d. (Box 790)
  - Family, Public Housing, Immigration raids, Interrogatories, Hospitals, n.d. (Box 791)
  - Bellow, Gary - Civil practice and procedure (Box 791)
  - Sutherland, Shirley Jean (Box 791)
  - Sutherland, Shirley Jean (Box 792)
  - Sutherland, Shirley Jean (Box 793)
  - Mickey v. Municipal, Court of the Los Angeles Judicial District, n.d. (Box 793)
  - Mickey v. State of California, n.d. (Box 793)
  - Cohen v. People of the State of California f.1, n.d. (Box 793)
  - Cohen v. People of the State of California f.2, n.d. (Box 794)
  - Earl Caldwell and the New York Times 1969- 1972 v. United States of America, f. 1,2 (Box 795)
  - People v. Caswell, People v. Chacon, People v. Cohen, Cook v. Eastman Kodak Co, People v. Cowgill, n.d. (Box 795)
  - Cowling v. California -- Cortines v. Scott, n.d. (Box 796)
  - Mental Commitment, Homosexual, Housing Discrimination, Housing Proposition, Court cases, n.d. (Box 796)
  - Julian Bond case, Spock, 1969- 1972 (Box 797)
  - Grand Jury -- Health, 1969-1972 (Box 797)
  - Mental - insanity laws, School suit backgrounder (original), 1969-1972 (Box 797)
  - Education -- First Amendment, 1969- 1972 (Box 798)
  - Prostitution, 1974-1975 (Box 798)
  - Socialist Workers 1974 California Campaign Committee v. Edmund G. Brown, Jr, 1974-1975 (Box 799)
  - Socialist Workers 1974 California Campaign Committee v. Edmund G. Brown, 1974-1975 (Box 800)
  - Oil reports, publications, policies., 1974-1975 (Box 801)
  - Oil- other environmental cases (non-oil) (H), 1974-1975 (Box 802)
  - The Oil Import Question, Social Workers 1974 California Campaign Committee v. Edmund G. Brown, Jr., 1974-1975 (Box 803)
  - Socialist Workers 1974 California Campaign Committee, v. Edmund G. Brown, Jr,. Proposition 9 (The Political Reform Act) Handbook, 1974-1975 (Box 804)
  - Study of outer continental shelf lands of the United States report, County of Santa Barbara v. Walter Hickel, 1974-1975 (Box 805)
  - County of Santa Barbara v. Walter Hickel, Draft Environmental Statement, 1974-1975 (Box 806)
  - County of Santa Barbara v. Rogers C. B. Morton, 1974-1975 (Box 807)
  - Address Cards, Seminar Response Cards, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Report on August 17th hearing, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Endowment, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Foundations Board, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Slaff Event, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Institute of Money Management, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Foundation contributors, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Taxes, endowment, grants, etc., 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Materials pertaining to taxes, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - 1981 directory, Roger Baldwin, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Advertising for deferred giving, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - ACLU board meetings, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Accounts recievable for Slaff and Chaplin events, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Fundraising event ideas, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Celebrity personalities for fundraisers, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Gay rights, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Solicitor 2nd Letter, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Gift range chart, 1974-1975 (Box 808)
  - Pledge Forms, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Foundation grants and proposals, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Foundation labels, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Large donor solicitation research, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Feminist Forum, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Alexander, David, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Lawyer Lists, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Budget, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Northern California large donor efforts, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Background-large donors, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - End of year fundraising campaign, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - End of year campaign, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Deferred Giving, 1974-1975 (Box 809)
  - Jewish Council, donors listing, 1974-1975 (Box 810)
  - Health Care, Homosexuals, Mental Health, 1965-1972 (Box 810)
  - Talbot, Dorman F. Jr- court case, 1967-1969 (Box 810)
  - Inovice for typesetting letterhead, 1983 (Box 810)
  - Fundraising Materials, 6 month plan, Kinoy, Arthur, Lawyer's Documents, Minor, Laura Murphy memoranda, 1979-1983 (Box 810)
  - Nuebone events, Ostrow, Laurie, Tax Notes, Seminars, Right to Die Committee, Kidder & Peabody & Co., 1974-1975 (Box 811)
  - Foundation Board Nominating Committee, Search for New Board Members, Restructuring Board Committee, 1982-1984 (Box 812)
  - Obituaries, 1983 (Box 812)
  - Planned giving, general, 1983 (Box 812)
  - Sinclair, Kennedy, 1981 (Box 812)
  - ACLU Foundation Board Meetings, 1983 (Box 812)
  - Stark, Leland A. - estate plan, 1982 (Box 812)
  - 1983 Board of Directors (Box 812)
  - Taxes, estate planning, 1980-1981 (Box 812)
  - Philanthropy Tax Institute - participants, 1980-1981 (Box 812)
  - Fundraising, planned giving, 1983 (Box 812)
  - Estrada Wanda J -- Floyd, Larry, 1978-1981 (Box 812)
  - Eiden, Richard -- Hancock, William B., 1968-1982 (Box 813)
  - Harder -- Jiminez, Eduardo f.1, 2, 1978- 1982 (Box 814)
  - Jiminez, Eduardo f.3 -- Hardin, Sandra, 1971-1980 (Box 815)
  - Hanselman, James -- Centro De Aztlan v. LAPD, 1972- 1980 (Box 816)
  - Aztlan v. Burns -- Coronado, 1972- 1978 (Box 817)
  - Draft - Zimmerman Case -- Education, general, 1966 - 1972 (Box 818)
  - Education, racial violence -- Education, school tax base, funds, 1966 - 1972 (Box 819)
  - Education, school suit, Union Oil Co., 1970-1973 (Box 820)
  - Oil - Freedom of Information case, lease suspension and terminations, legislative, 1970-1973 (Box 821)
  - Oil - legislative, Louisiana oil lease controversy. Women's names., 1969-1977 (Box 822)
  - Women Truck Drivers, Insurance, Abortion, Title VII, 1974-1977 (Box 823)
  - Sex discrimination in education athletics, Abortion, Hyde amendment, 1975- 1978 (Box 824)
  - ERA, Women's Credit, Discrimination in Athletics, Prostitution - Hartway v. People, 1974-1984 (Box 825)
  - Employment/unions - workers' rights, education. Integration, white flight, 1974- 1985 (Box 826)
  - Education, Proposition X, Law Schools, ACLU California Legislative Office, 1974- 1989 (Box 827)
  - Sex discrimination, Comparable Worth, Courts, 1972- 1983 (Box 828)
  - Church / state, 1973- 1983 (Box 829)
  - Church /state, 1981- 1984 (Box 830)
  - Courts/ trials rights - death penalty, American Bar Association, attorney fees, 1981-1985 (Box 831)
  - Courts/trial rights, 1977-1981 (Box 832)
  - Courts/trial rights, Welfare, 1973- 1984 (Box 833)
  - Healthcare - Aids. Free speech, 1978- 1985 (Box 834)
  - Free speech - pornography, holocaust, defamation, KKK, Shokie Case, 1978-1982 (Box 835)
  - Education- student's rights, quality of integrated education, integration, 1975- 1984 (Box 836)
  - Education- integration, Prop 9, curriculum. Courts/trial rights- death penalty, 1974- 1984 (Box 837)
  - Courts/trial rights- death penalty. Health care- general, National Conference of Christians, right to die, 1976-1985 (Box 838)
  - Health care- right to die, medical experimentation, rights of mentally ill, Ross Johnson Initiative, 1972- 1984 (Box 839)
  - Welfare- Ross Johnson Initiative, rights of the poor, poverty, hunger, Jobs with Peace, 1981-1985 (Box 840)
  - First Amendment, Housing, Nuclear power/ freeze, 1967- 1983 (Box 841)
  - Nuclear Hazards, First Amendment, Right to Die., 1977- 1983 (Box 842)
  - Legal Services, Social Security, Insurance, Housing, Non-profits., 1977- 1985 (Box 843)
  - International rights, foreign aid, War Powers Act, Human Rights Conference, 1982- 1985 (Box 843)
  - Immigration, 1979-1988 (Box 844)
  - Immigration, Free speech, Central America, 1982- 1985 (Box 845)
  - Central America, crimes, prostitutions, Law enforcement- surveillance, 1978- 1985 (Box 846)
  - Law enforcement, 1977-1985 (Box 847)
  - Law enforcement, legislation, government, 1979-1984 (Box 848)
  - Media, Military, Criminal Code, Gay rights, National Security, Impeachment of Nixon, Freedom of Information Act, 1973- 1984 (Box 849)
  - Freedom of Information Act, 1982-1983 (Box 850)
  - Freedom of Government Act, Government- Central America, Immigration/Travel, 1976-1985 (Box 851)
  - Immigration/ travel, 1974-1985 (Box 852)
  - Immigration/travel, Law enforcement, 1980-1985 (Box 853)
  - Law Enforcement, Olympic Games, 1975-1983 (Box 854)
  - Race/Racism, Aids, Trans rights, Sex discrimination, Parents rights, Elderly rights, Juvenile rights, 1975-1985 (Box 855)
  - Juvenile Rights, Gay rights, 1979- 1985 (Box 856)
  - Gay rights, Affirmative Action, Black -Americans rights, 1973-1985 (Box 857)
  - Playboy, Western Goals litigation, Police surveillance, PDID Settlement, 1978-1984 (Box 858)
  - PDID-case, Veteran's Rights, Affirmative Action, Rights of the Disabled, Community Relations Conference of Southern California, Minorities, Japanese-Americans, 1978- 1985 (Box 859)
  - Asian and Black Americans, Gay rights, Weber case, Bakke case, Animal rights, Juvenile Rights, 1978-1983 (Box 860)
  - Open Forum, Prisoners' Rights, Women's Rights- Olympics, FACT, 1980-1985 (Box 861)
  - Women's Rights, 1978-1985 (Box 862)
  - Women's Rights, Military Service, Media, Civil Liberties, 1975- 1985 (Box 863)
  - Privacy Rights, Prisoners' Rights, 1978-1985 (Box 864)
  - Prisoner's Rights, Women's Rights, 1978-1985 (Box 865)
  - Women's Rights, Privacy, 1978- 1985 (Box 866)
  - Politics, 1949-1987 (Box 867)
  - Politics, Personal Security, 1977-1985 (Box 868)
  - Personal Security, violence, 1978- 1985 (Box 869)
  - Personal Security, Voter registration, Political Process, Education, Parties, Political Groups, 1977-1985 (Box 870)
  - Parties, Political Groups, Governor Brown, 1977- 1984 (Box 871)
  - Health Rights Project, Gray v. L.A., Garza v. Reagan, Chavez v. Bohmlein, etc., n.d. (Box 1135)
  - Foundation Correspondence, Ceta Health Project, etc. (Box 1177)
  - Skyhorse- Mohawk, Student Rights, Goldberger Units, A.L. Wirin (Box 1178)
  - CCHPP Conference, LA Street Scene, Typewriting, Beverly Hills Bar Foundation (Box 1179)
  - Ed. Law File & Statistics,, Medical & Health Services, Mental Commitment, Bibliography- Civil Liberties, 1975, n.d. (Box 1180)
  - Med. Health Services, People of the State of California v. Terrazas -- Plunkett v. Wagner, Blake v. City of LA (Vol. 3), 1977, n.d. (Box 1181)
  - Reproductive Rights Defense Comm., Lantz v. LA Community College Dist. -- Norton Sound (Box 1182)
  - Oyarzo -- Patronite v. Proud, n.d. (Box 1183)
  - Patronite v. Proud, Lewis Burke, Maple Properties File #2, etc., 1981, n.d. (Box 1184)
  - Maple Properties File #3, Maple Properties v. Harris, 1982, n.d. (Box 1185)
  - Marina Point v. Wolfson, Socialist Workers Party, n.d. (Box 1186)
  - Socialist Workers Party, n.d. (Box 1187)
  - Joint Council of Interns and Res. v. Board of Supervisors, et al. (Box 1189)
  - Joint Council of Interns v. Bd. of Supervisors, n.d. (Box 1188)
  - Petition for Writ, Request For Immediate Temporary Stay, Exhibits A- A1, K-AA, n.d. (Box 1190)
  - Petitioners Exhibits B-J, WWG, n.d. (Box 1191)
  - WWCG, Lopez v. CA, Intervenors, etc., n.d. (Box 1192)
  - Executive and Nominating Comm. Ballot, 1978-1981 (Box 1193)
  - Chrono: January-February 1979. Ballots: 1977, 1979 (Box 1194)
  - Chrono: March- October 1979 (Box 1195)
  - Chrono: January- August 1978, November- December 1979 (Box 1196)
  - Chrono: September- December 1978, February- April 1981 (Box 1197)
  - Chrono: January- April 1981, May- June 1981 (Box 1198)
  - Chrono: May-November 1980 (Box 1199)
  - Chrono: December 1980, July- November 1981 (Box 1200)
  - Chrono: December 1981, ACLU 1980 Board, By-Laws, Committees, etc. (Box 1201)
  - Esquire Jan 1970 Magazine. Form Letters, Legislative Bulletin, Previews, Requests, etc., n.d. (Box 1202)
  - Ramona Ripston Clippings. "A" - "C" Materials, Women's Rights Projects, etc. (Box 1203)
  - "D"- "U" Materials, n.d. (Box 1204)
  - "V"- "Z" Materials, ACLU Reports, By-Laws, etc., n.d. (Box 1205)
  - Committee Choices, Affirmative Action, Immigration, Equality, etc., 1977-1981 (Box 1206)
  - Chapter Meeting Survey, Wirin Award, Legal Committee, etc., 1980-1981, etc. (Box 1207)
  - Copyright, Corporate Papers, Pregnancy Leave, n.d. (Box 1208)
  - Crime, Sanctuary, AIDS, Incest, Exclusionary Rule, n.d. (Box 1209)
  - Memos, Office Procedure, Manual, News, etc., 1986, n.d. (Box 1210)
  - Department of Public Social Services Files, etc., n.d. (Box 1212)
  - Financial Statements, Budget Reports, 1971-1984 (Box 1213)
  - Statements, Budgets, Minutes, 1974-1982 (Box 1214)
  - Motion to Compel Kelley, n.d. (Box 1215)
  - CIA Documents, Electronic Surveillance, etc., n.d. (Box 1216)
  - Receipts, Statements, Minutes, Declarations, etc., n.d. (Box 1217)
  - 1st Amendment, Judo, Dist. Court Bills, I.R.C., etc. (Box 1218)
  - 1st Amendment: Freedom of Assembly, Press, etc. (Box 1219)
  - 1st Amendment: Freedom of Speech, Press. Knight v. Kissinger. (Box 1220)
  - Violence, Cautionary Instructions, Rape, Wrongful Deaths, Intimidation, Gun Control, Prostitution, n.d. (Box 1224)
  - Voting, Elections, Parties, n.d. (Box 1225)
  - Fluoridation, Health, Welfare, Poverty Rights, Children's Rights, n.d. (Box 1226)
  - Health Care, Welfare, Poverty Rights, etc., n.d. (Box 1227)
  - Robbins Amendment/ Prop 1, Legislation, School Integration,etc., 1979-81, n.d. (Box 1228)
  - Brown Case 25th Anniversary Proclamation, School Integration: Kansas City, Boston, Topeka, and other Cities (Box 1229)
  - School Integration: San Diego, San Francisco, and other cities. Metropolitan Plan, Legislation, 1979-1980, n.d. (Box 1230)
  - Class Actions, ACLU Gay Rights Chapter, 1980 Observer Reports, etc., n.d. (Box 1231)
  - Privacy, Violence, Rape, Prisons, n.d. (Box 1232)
  - Planned Giving, Fundraising Asst., Sterilization, Library Records, Gun Control, Prisoners' Rights, 1984, n.d. (Box 1233)
  - Court Orders, Senators Torres/Crauston, Franklin Orosco, etc., n.d. (Box 1234)
  - ACLU Board Meetings, Jan 15, 1975 - Dec 15, 1976 (Box 1235)
  - ACLU Board Meetings, Jan 1973 - Dec 1975 (Box 1236)
  - Foundation Financial Statements (1967-1981), Board Meeting (July-December 1977), etc. (Box 1237)
  - ACLU National Steering Committee, Chapter Council (1977-82), Biennial Conference (1981), Foundation Board (1978-1982) (Box 1238)
  - Biennial Conference (1978-79), National Figures (1976). Steering Committee (1974-77) (Box 1239)
  - LAPD and Police Files (Box 1211)
  - Police Chief Davis' Removal, Police Budget, etc., n.d. (Box 1221)
  - Rosenberg Case, Police Reports, Statistics, Review Board, Communications System, etc., n.d. (Box 1222)
  - Speaker's Kit, Gun Control, Search and Seizure, Exclusionary Rule, Sheriff's Office, etc. (Box 1223)
  - Legislative Newsletter -- N.Y. Affiliate- Legislation Bulletins, 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 1240)
  - Election Reform -- LA Chapter Revision, 1968-1969, n.d. (Box 1241)
  - Day in Sacramento Legislative Lobby -- Election Information Ballot Propositions, 1966, 1972-1973, n.d. (Box 1242)
  - Michigan Coalition to End Government Spying -- Citizens' Commission Current (Box 1243)
  - Legal Profession, Courts, Trial Rights, etc., n.d. (Box 1244)
  - NLG Executive Board, National Lawyers Guild Convention, Legal Profession, 1974-76, n.d. (Box 1245)
  - Immigration, Travel, International Rights, Housing, etc., 1975-1977 (Box 1246)
  - Foreign Places, Intl. Rights, ASFC, Immigration, etc., 1973, 1974, n.d. (Box 1247)
  - Local Area, Law Enforcement/ Intelligence/ Police, Abuse and Killings, Alcohol, etc. (Box 1248)
  - ACLU Office, Lobbying, Life Insurance, etc., n.d. (Box 1249)
  - Barnes, Dorissa -- Stuewe, Erich F., ACLU Legislation, n.d. (Box 1250)
  - "A", "B" Correspondence, Insurance, CARS, Sample Letters, Membership Recruitment (Box 1251)
  - "C" -- "K" Correspondence (Box 1252)
  - "L"-- "P" Correspondence, Projects, Prisoners' Rights/ Jails/ Prisons (Box 1253)
  - Privacy/ Invasion of Privacy, California Institutions for Women, Prisons, n.d. (Box 1254)
  - Abortion, Privacy (through 1977), Drugs, n.d. (Box 1255)
  - Speaking Engagements, Caplins, CAR, n.d. (Box 1256)
  - RR- Personal, n.d. (Box 1257)
  - Juvenile Detention Facilities, Alpha File, Abuse, Rights/Minorities etc., n.d. (Box 1258)
  - Women's Rights, Minority Rights etc, n.d. (Box 1259)
  - NORML, Drugs, n.d. (Box 1260)
  - Privacy: Sexual, Sterilization, Records, etc., n.d. (Box 1261)
  - State Legislature, Media Publications, Crime, Violence/ Intimidation/ Gun Control, Privacy, n.d. (Box 1262)
  - KCET, Radio/Television, ACLU/ Media Publications, n.d. (Box 1263)
  - Amnesty, Military Service, Kust, 1973-1976, n.d. (Box 1264)
  - Legal Services, Health/ Welfare/ Poverty Rights, Medical Rights, Military Rights, n.d. (Box 1265)
  - Mental Health/ Rights, n.d. (Box 1266)
  - File Shredding, Law Enforcement/ Intelligence, Gangs, Informers, Housing, etc., n.d. (Box 1267)
  - FBI, CIA, Intelligence Agencies, n.d. (Box 1268)
  - Police, LEAA, Loitering, National Security, Halperin, ACLU v. FBI Case, IRS, FOIA, n.d. (Box 1269)
  - Death Penalty Sentence, Police, n.d. (Box 1270)
  - Citizens Advisory Committee, Education/ Schools/ Students' Rights, Sentences, Death Penalty, etc., n.d. (Box 1271)
  - Censorship, Free Speech/ Press/ Association, Integration, etc., n.d. (Box 1272)
  - Free Speech/ Press/ Association, Courtroom/ Fair Trial, etc., n.d. (Box 1273)
  - National ACLU Board of Directors, National Activity Reports, Free Speech, etc., n.d. (Box 1274)
  - ACLU Affiliates, National Committees, Elections, Meetings, Conference Totals, Associates, Press Releases, n.d. (Box 1275)
  - Affirmative Action, Minorities/Women, ACLU Affiliates Northern California, New York, 1975-1977, n.d. (Box 1276)
  - SCLC, CRCSC, Minorities/Women's Rights, NAACP, etc., n.d. (Box 1277)
  - Indian/ Native American Rights, Minorities/ Women, Gay Rights (Box 1278)
  - ACLU Committee and Other Reports, Legal Staff Committee, Bd. Meetings, 1977, 1980 (Box 1279)
  - School Integration, White Flight, Board Meetings, etc., 1979, n.d. (Box 1280)
  - Free Speech/ Press/ Association, Students, UCLA, Affirmative Action, n.d. (Box 1281)
  - Students, Schools, Employment/ Labor/ Worker's Rights, Discrimination, Taxes, etc., 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 1282)
  - Children & Youth, Juvenile Justice/ Law/ Rights, 1970, 1972, 1979, n.d. (Box 1283)
  - Children & Youth Rights, Women's Rights, etc., 1974-1979 (Box 1284)
  - Juries, Courts, Trials Rights, Women's Project, Affirmative Action, etc., 1978- 1980, n.d. (Box 1285)
  - Criminal Justice, Courts/ Trial Rights, Juries, etc., n.d. (Box 1286)
  - Human Rights, Trial Rights, Courts, Cases, etc., n.d. (Box 1287)
  - Chrono, Dec 72, Nov- Dec 73, May - Dec 74 (Box 1288)
  - "Q" - "Z", n.d. (Box 1289)
  - School Integration, Evaluations, Cases, etc., n.d. (Box 1290)
  - School Integration, Legislation, Metropolitan Plan, etc., n.d. (Box 1291)
  - School Integration, ACLU Policies -- Community Control, n.d. (Box 1292)
  - School Integration, Education, Community Involvement, etc., 1974-1975, n.d. (Box 1293)
  - Watergate, Law Enforcement/ Intelligence/ Police, School Integration, etc., n.d. (Box 1294)
  - National Legislation, Nixon, Watergate, etc., n.d. (Box 1295)
  - Personnel, Job Application Form, Legislation, Criminal Code, etc., n.d. (Box 1296)
  - Bycel, Ben -- Slaff, George, n.d. (Box 1297)
  - Sheinbaum, Smith, ACLU Policy (Box 1298)
  - Abortion, ACLU Activity Report (Box 1299)
  - KKK, Minorities, Women's Rights, Abortion, Privacy, n.d. (Box 1300)
  - Chapter Events, Council, Projects, Statistics, Survey, n.d. (Box 1301)
  - ACLU- Gay Rights, Dockets, 1972-1977, 1980-1981 (Box 1302)
  - Children and Youth Committee, Women's Rights, ACLU Board, 1979-1980 (Box 1303)
  - Election Committee, Children and Youth Committee, etc., 1978-1980 (Box 1304)
  - Women's Rights, Groups, Name Changes, etc., n.d. (Box 1305)
  - Prisons, Jails, Prisoner's Rights, etc., n.d. (Box 1306)
  - Sybil Brand Institute for Women, Prisoner's Rights, Inmates of SBI v. Supreme Court, etc. (Box 1307)
  - SBI Files, n.d. (Box 1308)
  - Sybil Brand Defendant's Discovery, Attorney Fees and Costs, Dr. Walter Kearns (Box 1309)
  - SBI Defendant's Discovery, Prison/Jail Inmate Letters and Correspondence, 1974-1978, n.d. (Box 1310)
  - Prison/ Jail Inmate Letters, Correspondence, etc., 1974-1977, n.d. (Box 1311)
  - Daniel Alesi -- Melvin Young, etc., n.d. (Box 1312)
  - SBI Court Clips #1-3, n.d. (Box 1313)
  - SBI Court Clips #4-6, n.d. (Box 1314)
  - LAPD Response to CAO Audit, Resource Allocation, Detention Tank Log (Box 1315)
  - SBI Inmates v. the County of LA, Peter J. Pitchess Vol. 1., etc., 1980, n.d. (Box 1316)
  - SBI Inmates v. The County of LA, Peter Pitchess Vol. 2-4 (Box 1317)
  - SBI Inmates v. LA: Appeal, Vol. 1-6, n.d. (Box 1318)
  - SBI Manual, SBI Inmates v. County of L.A., 1975, n.d. (Box 1319)
  - SBI Appellate Brief, Serrano v. Unruh, n.d. (Box 1320)
  - SBI Plaintiffs' Interrogations, Medical Trial Materials, Class Action Motions, Discovery, n.d. (Box 1321)
  - SBI Plaintiffs' Interrogations, Discovery III, IV, n.d. (Box 1322)
  - Sybil Brand Main File, Post Trial Brief, Working File, Plaintiffs' Discovery I (Box 1323)
  - SBI Trial Briefs, Findings and Judgement, Pre Trial (Box 1324)
  - SBI Post Trial Relief, Main File 2, n.d. (Box 1325)
  - SBI Inmates v. Pitchess, Depositions, Medical Manual Sheriff's Dept., Medical Testimony and Evidence (Box 1326)
  - SBI Inmates v. County of L.A., Depositions, n.d. (Box 1327)
  - Executive Committee, Garden Parties, Bill of Rights Dinners, 1974-1977 (Box 1328)
  - General Correspondence, Enemy List Dinner, Foundation Events, Nominating and Executive Committees, 1975-1977, n.d. (Box 1329)
  - Board of Directors, Lawyers Committee, ACLU Individual Attorneys, Minutes, 1983-1984, n.d. (Box 1330)
  - Executive Committee, Bd. of Directors, 1983-1984 (Box 1331)
  - Call Records, Bd. of Directors, Executive Committee, 1983-84, 1986 (Box 1332)
  - Call Records, 1985-1986 (Box 1333)
  - Foundation Board, Foundation Events, 1977- 1983 (Box 1334)
  - Nominating Committee, Budget Management Committee, Statements, Foundation Board, 1979- 1987 n.d. (Box 1335)
  - HUAC, HISC-- Legislative Committees by Chapter Area, 1969, n.d. (Box 1336)
  - CDC -- County Bd. of Supervisors, etc., n.d. (Box 1337)
  - Abraham, Ruth -- Complete Legislative Packet, 1971-1974, n.d. (Box 1338)
  - Affirmative Action -- Biennial Conference, Boulder, Colorado, 1972, n.d. (Box 1339)
  - Schools, International Affairs, Death Penalty, etc., n.d. (Box 1340)
  - Prop 21: Californians against Segregated Schools -- Wire Tapping, n.d. (Box 1341)
  - Pollution-- Prop II, Chrono, 1977, n.d. (Box 1342)
  - Chrono, 1976-1977 (Box 1343)
  - Chrono, 1975-1976 (Box 1344)
  - Chrono, 1975 (Box 1345)
  - Chrono, 1983 (Box 1346)
  - Chrono, 1982 (Box 1347)
  - Chrono, 1982, 1984 (Box 1348)
  - Chrono, 1984 (Box 1349)
  - Chrono, 1983 (Box 1350)